

## Jennifer L. Brown

811 Calais Street, Bellevue, NE 68123 Home: 816-536-4349 Cell: 816-536-4349 jennifer.l.brown79@gmail.com

#### **Career Overview**

A Web Designer and Developer experienced in the field of web programming, with skills in designing, development optimization of web applications and 12 years of experience in Information Technology/Security, Network Administration, Internet Security, Client Support Administration, and more.

### **Qualifications**

- Web Content Management
- Database Servers
- Technical Help Desk Experience
- Information Security
- · GUI and Tools
- Excellent Problem Solving Skills

- Strong Analytical Skills
- Proficiency in TCP/IP Protocols
- Project Management
- Document Management
- Development and Design Principles of Process

#### **Professional Skills**

- JavaScript, jQuery
  - ActionScript, FLEX, Flash
  - PHP, MySQL
  - XHTML, HTML, HTML5

Information Management Specialist

- CSS, CSS3
- DOM, FlashLite

- Python, Node.js, AngularJS
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Object Oriented Programming
- Responsive Web Design
- App Development
- Microsoft Operating Suite

- XML, API
- GIT
- Interface Design and Structure
- Digital Video and Audio CODECs
- MAMP

## **Experience**

**United States Air Force,** Strategic Air Command (STRATCOM), Offutt AFB, Nebraska Knowledge Operations Management Craftsman

United States Air Force, Air Combat Command (ACC), Whiteman AFB, Missouri

January 2000 – October 2009

October 2009 – June 2012

United States Air Force, Technical School (TS), Biloxi, Mississippi

October 1999 – December 1999 August 1999 – October 1999

United States Air Force, Technical School (18), Blioxi, Mississippi United States Air Force, Basic Military Training (BMT), Lackland AFB, Texas

**Education** 

Full Sail University

Bachelor of Science: Web Design and Development

Winter Park, Florida, USA

**June 2014** 

# Accomplishments/Awards

2014 Web Design and Development Advanced Achievement Award Joint Service Commendation Medal, STRATCOM, USAF Air Force Commendation Medal, ACC, USAF June 2014 August 2011 October 2008